<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lev Zakharov</title><link>https://lzakharov.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Lev Zakharov</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lzakharov.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reading</title><link>https://lzakharov.github.io/reading/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:42:32 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://lzakharov.github.io/reading/</guid><description>Presentations Scala Implicits, Lev Zakharov (2019) Books &amp;amp; Papers Software Engineering Terraform: Up &amp;amp; Running, 2nd edition, Yevgeniy Brikman Elasticsearch in Action, Matthew Lee Hinman, Radu Gheorghe, and Roy Russo User Story Mapping: Discover the Whole Story, Build the Right Product, Jeff Patton Kubernetes: Up and Running, Kelsey Hightower, Brendan Burns and Joe Beda The Pragmatic Programmer, David Thomas and Andrew Hunt The Little Book of Semaphores, Allen B. Downey Microservices Patterns, Chris Richardson Test-Driven Web Development with Python, Harry J.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://lzakharov.github.io/blog/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://lzakharov.github.io/blog/intro/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello Everyone!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://lzakharov.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://lzakharov.github.io/resume/</guid><description>Senior Golang developer with Team Lead experience.
Education Kazan Federal University, Institute of Information Technology and Intelligent Systems, 2014-2018, Applied Computer Science. Skills Programming Languages: Golang, Python Databases: PostgreSQL, ElasticSearch, Redis, S3, ClickHouse Message Brokers: Kafka CI/CD: Drone CI, GitLab CI Languages: Russian (native), English (upper-intermediate) Other: Git, GitLab, Jira, Docker, Kubernetes, Helm, Terraform (+ Terragrunt), Yandex Cloud, Swagger, Postman, Protobuf, gRPC, GraphQL, Apollo, Kibana, Prometheus, Grafana, Jaeger, Clean Architecture, Microservices, Functional Programming Work Experience SberMarket, Golang Developer at PaaS Team (10.</description></item></channel></rss>